can you name Putin Yes for Here he is since
можете назвать что Путин Да за Вот он с
ninety-nine in power what has
девяносто девятого года при власти что
he done for your picked up vka for 20
он сделал для вашей подхватило вки за 20
plus years How what did he do for example for me
плюс лет Как что сделал он например мне
today this year even this year
сегодня вот в этом году даже в этом году
here
вот
uh raised my pension by
ээ пенсию поднял на
75% Good evening I am from the city of Khmelnitsky where are
75% Добрый вечер я из города Хмельницкий
you from I am from the city from the city from the
Вы откуда Я из города из горда из
Oryol region
Орловской области
what have you heard more than once Oryol region
что вы не раз слышали Орловская область
tin What city city village village
олов Какой город
I am in the village You don't
город село село я вот в селе Вы же не
know anything there why this is unnecessary
знаете там ничего зачем это лишняя для
information for you it means nothing to you it is
вас информация она для вас ничего не
interesting I am interested I am a
знает интересно Мне интересно я яль я
villager So if you have any
сельский житель Так что вот если есть
questions I will try to answer if I From
вопросы постараюсь ответить если я С
what locality are
какого населённого пункта
you called a village picked up vka I
вы называется дере деревня подхватило
understood everything picked up and What is this
вка всё понял подхватило а Какой это
district Krasnyansky district
район район краснянский
picked up vka Kromskoy district of the Oryol region
подхватило вка кромской район Орловской
writes picked up vka and Kromskoy Yes
области пишет подхватило вка а кромской
it used to be Trostyansky Yes Yeah I
Дада он раньше тростянский был Дада Ага
understood yes there is such a thing Yes picked up I understood
понял да есть такое Да подхватило понял
what you mean you moved to live in a pension to
о чём вы вы так переехали на пенсию жить
pick up vka  or there all my life No I'm there I'm
в подхватило или там всю жизнь Нет я там
there all my life all my life there is not there And
я там всю жизнь всю жизнь есть не там А
here all my life yes That is, you just like a
здесь всю жизнь да То есть вы вот прямо
native
коренной
picked up yes picked up vec yes here is a
подхватило да подхватило вец да вот
collective farmer I understood I understood and the World Cup you
колхозник я понял понял а ЧМ вы
picked up vec want to talk to me
подхватило вец хотите поговорить со мной
Khmelnitsky woman
хмельничанка
I would also ask what's in the city and so well
Я бы ещё спросил что там в городе а так
what can I ask about your picked up vka
ну что я спрошу про вашу подхватило вку
Yes nothing snow is lying all around And you Why did you
Да ничего снег лежит кругом А вы Для
go to Roulette What did you want to
чего вышли в Рулетку О чём вы хотели
talk about with people from Ukraine so no And
поговорить с людьми из Украины так нет А
I'm just curious so I'm looking In general I
мне просто интересно вот смотрю В общем
went to Ukraine So I'm thinking this
вот на Украину зашёл Вот и думаю это
very thing Look what's there after all they have a
самое Глянь что там там всё-таки у них
war how are they what are they this very thing
война как они что они вот это самое
What are the prospects for this war maybe here is
Какие перспективы этой войне вот может
someone complaining about some kind of
быть вот кто-то жалуется на какую-то
life Well how can I
жизнь Ну как могу
calm you down Understand
успокою
Here is your picked up vka
Поня Вот ваша подхватило вка
gasified gasified
газифицирован газифицированные
percentage Well percentage now I'll say so so
процент Ну процент сейчас скажу так так
so this was sold This burned down
так это продали Вот это сгорело
14 houses were burned Yeah
сожгли 14 домов
4 houses are gasified yes yes yes yes And
Угу 4 домов газифицирован да да дада да
how many houses are there in total And in total A
А сколько всего там домов
total of houses there are Well shadows are
А всего А всего там домов Ну тени
cast Well somewhere houses  Approximately this
брошены Ну где-то домов Примерно это
same 16 two have already left And that is all, that is, out of
самое 16 два уже уехали И всё то есть из
16 houses 14 are gasified yes yes I understood that it was
16 домов 14 газифицирован да да понял то
picked up in some serious
это подхватило в какая-то серьёзная
village Like I see Well
такая деревня Типа я вижу
yes I understood And you from this picked up vki
Ну да понял И вы из этой подхватило вки
above in chat roulette to solve
выше в чат рулетку решать
geopolitical world issues I
геополитические мировые вопросы Я так
understand Yes yes of course of course
понимаю Да да конечно конечно
what to decide what to
коне что решать что
decide
решать
reached geopolitical world
дошло геополитические мировые
issues
вопросы
you
вы
clearly kitchen Conversations like this is sa that's
сно кухонные Разговоры вот так это са
when at one time as they say
вот когда в своё время как говорится
Brezhnev was scolded and then this same thing
Брежнев ругали вот а потом это самое
went out and this with the Soviet flag to the
выходили и это с флагом советским на
demonstration on November 7 and everyone
демонстрацию 7 ноября а все
scolded Cool yes But in vain well in
ругали Прикольно да А вот зря вот а вот
vain I at home scolded Brezhnev after all after
зря я дома ругали Брежнева всё-таки
all a good Ukrainian was
как-никак вот хороший украинец был
at Interesting but look here's an
у Интересно а вот смотрите вот
interesting question uh do I
интересный такой вопрос э-э я правильно
understand correctly that now uh well let's say from
понимаю что сейчас э-э ну скажем из
your picked up vki the youth are leaving
вашей подхватило вки молодёжь уезжает
there are probably no youth at all Yes
там наверное уже вообще нет молодёжи Да
and listen Yes I'm here the most important thing I
а слушайте Да я тут самое главное я своё
picked up mine That is, you are the only one left there
подхватил То есть вы там один остались
years old No, I'm not alone Well, there are
год Да не не один я остался Ну там есть
grandmothers there, well, old people there sometimes
там бабушки там ну старички там иногда
we'll get together for some project,
там сойдёмся там на какой проект там
drink some moonshine or something else like that Well,
самогоночка выпьем вот или что-то ещё
rarely of course, but mostly we
бывает такое Ну редко конечно а так в
sit at home in the snow Where are you in your
осном дома сидим по снегу Куда ты в
bolsters, getting to the bottom I
валиках дото
understand The question is an
пае Понял Вопрос такой вопрос да
interesting one for
интересный для
you, how can you call it Putin Yes, for
вас как вот можете назвать что Путин Да
He's been in power since 1999,
за Вот он с девяносто девятого года при
yes In fact, yes, for more than 20 years already,
власти да По сути да больше 20 лет уже
19 Yes, yes, more than 20 years, how can you
19 Да да больше 20 лет как бы можете мне
tell me what he's done for your
сказать что он сделал для вашей
picked up
подхватил
le How what did he do for me, for example,
ле Как что сделал он например мне
today, this year, even this year, he
сегодня вот в этом году даже в этом году
raised my pension by
вот пенсию поднял на
75%
75%
7.5 yes yes
7,5 да
And I I ask Why is it 7 per And they
да А я Я спрашиваю А почему 7 по А мне
told me That's the level of inflation we have according to the
сказали Такой размер инфляции у нас по
Constitution No, look, I'm pos Yes,
Конституции Нет смотрите вот я пос Да
what surprises me is 2022, inflation
вот меня что удиви вот 2022 год инфляция
in Russia is
в России
% in children Yes, in 2023, the
% в дет Да в двадцать третьем году
forecast is the forecast for inflation 7 with a pontoon yes Yeah,
прогноз прогноз инфляции 7 с поно
that is, va  your pension was increased
да Угу то есть ва вам увеличили пенсию
simply
просто
by the inflation index yes yes yes yes that's
на индекс инфляции да
it I understand it's interesting that
Да да да так и есть понял интересно то
is and in the World Cup
есть а в ЧМ заслуга
Putin's merit Putin's merit Well look
Путина заслуга Путина Ну посмотрите вот
if he can at least
если он может так вот пенсионеру хотя бы
compensate a pensioner for this inflation Well then that
компенсировать вот эту инфляцию Ну
means it's already a merit he's already trying to
значит это уже заслуга уже старается
do something for pensioners
что-то для пенсионеров сделать
you know
понимаете
like my My granddaughter for example here she is
как моя Моя внучка например вот она вот
she has a second child and here are
вот у неё второй ребёнок появился и вот
her prices let's do what you
ей цены давайте так как вы
think is real Wait wait I'm talking about
считаете реально Подожди подожди я про
you Grandfather no no I'm not interested in
тебя Дед говорю не не мне не интересно
fairy tales about a granddaughter I'm talking about you no you won't
сказки про внучку Я про тебя нет ты не
finish I'll talk to you about you
закончишь я буду говорить с тобой о тебе
not about some of yours In short
не о каких-то там ках твоих Короче
look let's do it
смотри давай
this way last year last year
так год за прошлый за прошлый год
proly go What do you think prices went up by
пролы го Как ты думаешь цены подорожали
more than
больше чем на
7% Of course more more yes then maybe the
7% Конечно больше больше да то может
real inflation rate is more than the
реальный уровень инфляции больше чем
declared
заявленный
7% maybe more more about So
7% может быть и больше больше о Так
maybe Putin is deceiving you Yes the
может Путин получается вас обманывает Да
real inflation rate is higher and he
реальный уровень инфляции больше а он
says look he 7 I'll raise your pension by 7%
говорит смотрите он 7 я вам на 7%
you Putin raised your pension by 7%
подниму пенсию вы Путин поднял на 7%
so
пенсию так
so you see how he raised it even a little bit
та видите как вот хоть чуть-чуть поднял
and that somehow makes us happy and not quite like they
и то нас как-то радует и не совсем чтобы
abandoned us, he
бросили нас вот заботится вот о народ
cares, he cares about the people, look, this is the same
заботится смотрите вот детям это самое
for the children Wait, I'm talking about you
Подождите про дети я про вас говорю
specifically about you, I don't need to talk about the children,
конкретно про вас не надо мне по детей
look, I'll talk to the children about the children, I'm talking to
смотри с детьми поговорю про детей я с
you about you, that is, I
тобой о тебе говорю вот то есть я
understand correctly, but look, Putin
правильно понимаю а вот смотри Путин о
cares about you, you say so, like
вас заботится ты так говоришь вот как
Putin is like your mother, yes It turns out
вроде Путин как мама ваша да Получается
that he cares about you, like he cares,
что он заботится о вас как он заботится
our dad, dad, dad, I understood, yes And
наш папа папа папа папа понял да А
look, who is more important, the people or
смотрите Кто главнее народ или
Putin No, of course, the people are more important for us,
Путин Нет конечно у нас народ главнее
because you put Putin in place, you put Putin in place, we do
потому что Путина поставили вы Путина
n't
поставили не
want you put Putin in place, yes, look,
хотим вы Путина поставили да то смотри
I understand correctly that Putin is
то я правильно понимаю что Путин - это
your hired worker Correct Correct, yes, that's exactly how I
ваш наёмный рабочий Правильно Правильно
understood it, yes
да именно так понял да
Question From whose money does he raise your
Вопрос Из чьих денег да повышает вам
pension, from ours, from yours, that is,
пенсию из наших из ваших то есть ещё раз
look again, Putin from your money raises
смотрите Путин из ваших денег повышает
your pension by the
вам пенсию на
level of inflation, which is actually lower than the
на уровень инфляции который реально ниже
real level of inflation, and you are happy about it,
реального уровня инфляции и вы от этого
yes, yes, yes, yes, not happy No, not happy
счастливы да дадада да не счастлив Нет
But just happy, happy,
не счастливы А просто довольны довольны
look again, let's do it this way  Putin
да ещё раз смотрите давайте так Путин
takes from your money so yes gives you a
берёт из ваших денег так да даёт вам
pension and you are happy with it gives a
пенсию и вы от этого довольны даёт
pension
пенсию
happy that is once again look Putin
довольны то есть ещё раз смотрите Путин
suits us Putin took your
нас это устраивает Путин взял ваши
money and gave
деньги и дал
you our money Yes yes Putin
вам наши деньги Да да Путин ваши деньги
gave you your money And what is Putin's merit
дал вам А в чём заслуга Путина
yes that he is an effective manager ONT to
да то что он эффективный менеджер ОНТ
manage our money no so look
управлять нашими деньгами нет так смотри
if he were no look an effective
если бы он был нет смотри эффективный
manager is if he raised your salary
менеджер это если бы он у вас зарплата
pension would increase more than the
повышала пенсия повышалась бы больше чем
inflation rate and I Boshe here Biden is an
на уровень инфляции и я Боше вот байден
effective manager there for example people in the
эффективный менеджер там например люди в
village Yes look you have a
дерев Да вот смотри у вас есть
car 40 40 trillion of
автомобиль 40 40 триллионов внешнего
Biden's external debt And
долга у байдена А
Biden oh-oh enough
байден ой-ой хватит
look I heard about this external debt yes
смотри Я слышал про этот внешний долг да
you you also give me this Zelensky
вы вы мне ещё этого само Зеленского
manager who with a
менеджер который
hat I can't understand look I can't
шапкой Я не могу понять смотрите Я не
understand wait grandpa Calm down Drink some
могу понять подожди дед Успокойся Выпей
valerian Look I can't understand
валерьянки Смотри я не могу понять вот у
America has 43 America has an external debt there look America has an
Америки 43 у Америки там смотри у
external debt but American grandpa
Америки внешний долг но американский дед
lives better than
живёт лучше
you Listen American you really
тебя Слушай американский ты реально в
picked up in yours VK  you let me
своей подхватило вке ты давай я тебе
turn off the sound for you grandpa in short and I'll
отключил звук дед короче и я тебе
tell you You just live when you
расскажу Ты просто живёшь когда ты
laugh with Biden some kind of their
смеёшься с байдена какой-то там у них
foreign debt is 43 million take any
внешний долг 43 млн возьми любого
American Yes your age and you
американца Да твоего возраста и тебя ты
really from your own VKI you never
реально из своей подхватило вки никуда
go anywhere And never went anywhere in your life
не выезжаешь И никуда в жизни не выезжал
and you damn went to Moscow once when
и ты в Москву блин ездил когда-то когда
in childhood You were taken to a pioneer camp
в детстве В пионерский лагерь тебя
You old grandpa
Ты старый дед
went hello hello
пошёл привет привет Ты
Where are you from you have a channel in my opinion Yes there is some kind of
откуда у тебя же канал по-моему Да
Yes where are you
какой-то какой-то есть Да ты
from I'm from Buryatia Listen is this electrical
откуда я с Бурятии Слушай это у тебя
tape on your
изолента на зарядке от
phone charger no not from the phone but what kind of
телефона нет не от телефона а что за
charger Yes it's
зарядочка
just not a charger but just a wire a
Да просто не зарядка а просто провод
wire I understand damn I haven't seen wires with electrical tape
провод понял блин Я провода с изолентой
since the temporary Soviet Union And
не видел с временно Советского Союза А
you don't use electrical tape Well
вы изолентой не пользуетесь Да вообще ну
anyway since the Soviet Union I don't
как бы я со врем Советского Союза не
remember that we just buy electrical tape a new
помню уже что изоленты мы просто новый
cord if anything And
Шнур покупаем если что А да
yes Well and
Ну и как
like what kind of cord is this Can you
бы а что это за Шнур такой можешь
show a simple cord what are
показать простой Шнур что
you well and what is it for
ты ну а к чему
yes it is from the charger then the charger for what
он да он от зарядки то зарядка для чего
for the phone phone I told you
для телефона телефона я тебе говорил
charger for the phone I saw on the cloud Well
зарядка для телефона я по облачку видел
what is the big deal I didn't understand And how much does a
Ну что такого-то я не понял А сколько
new
стоит новый
cord cost Yes I don't know 300 rubles probably And
шнурок Да не знаю рублей 300 наверно А
what can't you buy a new cord Well
что ты не можешь купить новый Шнур Ну
it works I
это же работает
understood correctly Well what is the problem it's not
правильно понял Ну а что проблема не
just interesting
просто интересно
sorry advice in the Soviet Union with electrical tape
соре совет в Советском Союзе изолентой
Yes I remember they would stick
Да помню лепили
anything and you are such a total [ __ ] in
угодно а ты такой вообще белоручка такой
general yes you don't do anything like that with
вообще да вот ничего такого не делаешь
your own hands Yes there the car breaks down you
своими руками Да там машина сломалась ты
go to the service Yes there run that's how it turns
идёшь в сервис Да там бежи так
out yes And I'll do it myself
получается да А я сам сделаю сам починю
I'll fix it myself Well if so somewhere the wire broke I'll fix it
Ну если так гдето прово переломился я
somewhere there somewhere I'll do something
его раз там подмо где-то что-то сделаю
he'll go on What is the problem I understood
он дальше поедет Что проблема-то понял
different approaches from Buryatia where From
разные подходы из Бурятии откуда Из
Ulan yes yes from Ulan Yes I understood what you're
улану да да из улану Да понял о чём
talking about
общаешься
yes About what and in different things I understood Listen
да О чём а в разном о всём понял Слушай
and how How do you think Why in this
а как Как ты считаешь Почему в этот в
Russia there is gold oil gas diamonds and
России есть золото нефть газ алмазы а
people live as poorly as
люди живут так бедно как
you And this is a mystery for everyone a mystery
ты А это вот загадка для всех загадка а
well  let's try to
ну давай попробуем
figure it out Well
разгадать Ну
try I think that someone is appropriating this money for
попробуй Я думаю что кто-то эти деньги
themselves
себе
what money what money Well, from oil and gas,
деньги какие деньги Ну от нефть и газа
gold,
золото
diamonds I'm
алмазов
appropriating And that someone is selling them
присваиваю А что их кто-то продаёт что
or something I don't understand Well, probably how is
ли или что не понят Ну наверное
that probably yes Well, like selling or
как это наверное да Ну типа продаёт или
not selling Well, they are selling yes Well, I don't know
не продаёт Ну продают же да Ну я не знаю
you see China India Yes China India is
ты видишь Китай Индия Да Китай Индия
buying
покупает
Yes but I don't need gold Oh wait
Да но мне золото не надо О подожди
tea Yes there's a calendar on the wall it's
чай Да там е календарь на стене
cool for a last year's
прикольно з а прошлогодний
calendar a mug with tea a mug such a
календарь кружка с чай кружка такая
nice atmosphere of course in Russian in Russian everything And
кайфу конечно по-русски по-русски всё А
this is your office right opposite the
это у тебя прямо кабинет прямо напротив
front door
входной двери
yes Well, yes there I have an entrance Yes somehow
да Ну да там Входная у меня Да как-то
everything is so compact the front door is right
так всё компактно входная дверь сразу же
there the office is right there the teapot it's cool
тут кабинет тут же чайник ту прикольно
ergonomic Here everything everything is close I
эргономично Здесь всё всё всё близко
understand next to you And listen, do you
понял рядышком А слушай а кружка У тебя
also have a mug from the Soviet Union
тоже от Советского Союза ещё осталась
This metal one is of
вот эта металлическая естественно
course Naturally they don't make these now of course they don't make them
Естественно таких сейчас не выпускают
and what
таких естно не делают а что у тебя есть
other modern mugs do you have Well, yes There's one like this
другие кружки
you see one with  I got it with
видишь такая с
roses,
розочками понял
cool, fork, look, fork, what
прикольно вилка смотри вилка Какая
aluminum, aluminum? Yes, it bends. Well,
алюминиевая алюминиевая Да она же гнётся
why isn't it written here, we have this
что это не написано у нас у нас же этот
plant, it turns out to be
завод получается
London, in short, this one. Yes, I see
Лондонский на ней короче этот Да я вижу
that it's aluminum. Fork, yes, like in the Soviet Union,
что это алюминиевая Вилка да как в совке
no, no, no, it's not. You see, it's ours,
не нене не она Видишь она наша именно
exactly, Buryat, yes. Well, it bends. It
Именно Бурятская да А ну она гнётся Она
really bends. That's aluminum, you can of course. That's cool. And what do you not have? And
реально гнётся Вот это алюминивая можешь
spoons, an aluminum spoon is also
а а ложки ложка алюминиевая тоже
available. Yes, of course, there is. Well, show me. It's not like that.
есть Да есть конечно А ну покажи она ж
Okay, spoons. I'll
типа така не блет Ладно ложки Я тебе
show you the knife now, wait a minute. This one
сейчас нож покажу сечас подожди Этот ещё
I don't know yet. What plant manufactured it, but
я не знаю како Какой завод исполнял но
it's under the number. Look
он короче под номером
here if you can make out the
Смотри здесь если Разглядишь
number here, you see. Understand. Understand. This is it. Show me. Show me. Well,
зде номе видиш Поня Поня это
I understood about the knife, yes, show me. There is an aluminum spoon.
я понял да покажи ложку есть алюминиевая
Yes, an aluminum spoon. Now,
Да алюминиевая ложка Сейчас
wait, no, aluminum. It looks like you already have
подожди алюминие нет Походу ты уже
aluminum. I do
алюминиевые у меня алюминиевый здесь
n't have aluminum here, you fool. I have one, in short, this one.
дуре нету у меня есть короче такой этот
scraper well this is
скребок ну это
an owl this is from a Soviet set do you have one
сове это с набо советского у вас он
like that too I am 100% sure that
такой тоже есть я я уверен в 100% что у
you have such there are such probably
вас такие есть есть такие наверно есть
yes well spoons aluminum spoons no yet
да ну ложки ложки алюминиевый нету пока
but there is no aluminum spoon here I
но ложки алюминиевый нету здесь у меня
already have such modern ones already here are
уже такие современные уже здесь такие
spoons Well show me this modern
идут ложки Ну покажи эту современную
spoon But I have forks In short look
ложку А зато у меня вилки Короче смотри
what old ones there are here they are well well this is a
какие старинные есть вот они нуста ну
Soviet Lona you are like this Yes I remember
ста это Советская Лона тя такая Да я пом
metal like this in Yes in Europe there are no such things
металличе такая в Да в Европе таких нету
100%
нету 100%
No well and so far that's all well such
Не ну и вот пока что Всё ну такая
a can opener you
открывашка
know
знае
this And what else a ladle Well a small porch
это А что ещ поварёшка Ну пор маленька А
Well show the ladle there are
ну покажи поварёшке шлаки есть
such slags Nama just what is such and such and it
такие Нама просто что такого-то а
turns out not just I looked that in
получается не просто я я смотрел что в
Russia there is a problem they do not produce Well with
России там проблема не выпускаю Ну с
pots in short these frying pans you do not
кастрюлями короче вот это сковородки у
have such Yes
вас нету такого Да кастрюль
we do not have pots everything on our hands We fry there Well
ского не мы же всё на руках Жарим там Не
I saw that like some kind of
ну я я видел что типа такие какие-то
iron bathhouses they use healthy But
баняки железные используют здоровы А
really there are  pots Show me Just for
реально есть кастрюли Покажи Ради
fun what kind of pots do you have We
интереса какие кастрюли у вас Мы
communicate normally Yes I don't
нормально общаемся как раз Да у меня
have any pots like that here now I don't have
нету сейчас таких здесь кастрюль я я
pots I'm telling you there are no Russians there are no
нету кастрюли Я же говорю нету россиян
pots there need to be somewhere in short well do
кастрюль нету нету надо гдето короче ну
you have a frying pan in the next
а сковородка есть у тебя следующую
country Yes no of course not either I'm all on
страну Да нету конечно тоже я всё на
that Well what about some dishes plates Well
этом Ну а какую-то посуду тарелки Ну
can you show me some dishes What kind do you have Everything I'm really
что-то можешь посуду показать Какая у
interested
вас как Всё Мне аж интересно
really I've never been to Buryatia
действительно Я никогда не был в Бурятии
I'm interested in how people
Мне интересно как люди там
live there Yes Listen it's normal People live here Well
живут Да Слушай нормально Здесь живут
can you show me some dishes I've
народы Ну можешь показать посуду
already shown you enough what's
я тебе уже показал хватит что
there
там
Show me Well come on show me something too yes
Покажи Ну давай мне тоже что-нибудь
sesh show something to everyone on the
покажи да сеш показывать всяким в
internet And what
интернете чтото А что
I well I
я ну
understood
понял
offended Yes I wasn't offended about offended
обиделся Да я не обиделся про обиделся
offended simply simply you offend and not
обиделся просто просто ты обижаешь а не
offended You were
обиделся Ты
offended by whom to be offended Well listen what do
обиделся на кого обижаться Ну слушай а
you How do you feel about the fact that there is a
как вы Как вы относитесь к тому что идёт
war What did you start
Война Ты себе что начал
Yes from spoons to war  yes yes
Да с ложек на на войну переключился да
And what kind of war is
да А какая Война
going on where What kind of war Well between NATO and
идёт где Какая война Ну между НАТО и
Russia
Россией
between
между
whom
кем
And between China and
А между Китаем и
Syria I don't know I haven't heard of such a thing I do
Сирии Я не знаю не слыхал про
n't even know anything to tell you about
не могу про
it I
это
understand what you
понял ты кем
do for a living I
работаешь
work on an aircraft carrier
работаем
what-what what's the question What do you do for a living
что-что в чём вопрос Кем
nobody I'm not a rap I don't work for nobody so I
никем Я не рап никем не работаю так
understand And how do you get money I don't
понял А как деньги получаешь
need money And how do you live and don't need it and what do you eat
никак мне деньги не нужны А за счёт чего
for I go I grow it
живёшь а не нуждаюсь в этом а еду за что
myself I grow it myself what Yes VS What do I need such I
иду сам
grow Well what are you growing everything I
выращ всё что мне
need about beauties Hello
потребно о красавиц Здравствуйте
[music]
[музыка]
of course background of course Magnificent Well and
конечно фон конечно Великолепный Ну и у
yours is not bad either Where are you
вас тоже неплохой Вы
from I'm from St. Petersburg
откуда Я из Питера О чём общаетесь
What are you talking about in St. Petersburg Well about what in your background it's
Питере Ну о чём н у тебя на заднем фоне
clear what about politics Of course Well in your
понятно о чём политике Конечно Ну у тебя
background it's also clear what about
на заднем фоне тоже понятно о чём об
economics I don't need Vintage yeah yeah
экономике у меня Винтаж не надо дадада
Vintage that's it in Russia there are so many Vintage
Винтаж вот та в России столько Винтаж
carpets now especially a representative of
ков сейчас особенно представитель
vintage dentistry
винтажной стоматологии
Well this It doesn't concern you much If
Ну это Это тебя мало касается Если
you want to say something smart about
хочешь что-то умное сказать по
Come on why  question Why does Russia have
Давай почему вопрос Почему Россия имеет
wealth oil gas gold diamonds and people
богатство нефть газ золото алмазы а люди
live in vintage
живут в винтажных
apartments, everyone lives as they want Yes,
квартирах кто как хочет так и живёт Да
why do people in America and Europe
почему вот люди в Америке и в Европе
want to live well and in Russia everything is
хотят жить хорошо а в России все
Vintage Well, they want it that way and we want it that way Yes,
Винтаж Ну они так хотят а мы так хотим
why do Russians want it that way Well,
Да почему вот русские так хотят Ну
because they want it Well, why, why do I
потому что хотят Ну почему почему вот я
want to understand the Russian soul Well,
хочу разобраться в русской душе Ну вот
for me, for example,
для меня например да вот
look, a simple thing I'll tell you simply
смотри простая вещь Я тебе скажу просто
and clearly for me, for example, when the
и ясно для меня например когда вот
Union fell apart and I, I, the Soviet Union, you see,
развалился союз а я я я Советский Союз
I was about like you Well, I was 40
понимаешь я был приблизительно как ты Ну
years old then, yeah, that's it In
мне было 40 лет тогда угу вот В
ninety-one, I was 40 years old
девяносто первом году мне было 40 лет
just like that Well,
как раз
this is
Вот и этот ну
what I like so much and
что мне так нравится а у меня Ностальгия
I have Nostalgia And I want it so much and wait a minute And should I
А я так хочу а минуточку А что я должен
report to someone about
перед кем-то отчитываться по поводу того
what I want or don't want What is this It doesn't
что я хочу или не хочу Это что Это са не
report, I'm just curious I
отчитывается просто вот мне интересно Я
want to understand why people like
хочу понять почему люди любят
Vintage Well, probably for some reason and especially since
Винтаж Ну наверное почему-то и тем более
you'll notice all these old ones I have
что ты заметишь вот эти все старинные
these very buffets and so yes, they are
вот у меня эти самые буфеты и так да они
very expensive by the way, I have
очень дорого стоят кстати
these  your doors and wallpaper are
име вот эти ваши двери и обои
antique doors mine are not antique I have
старинные двери у меня не старинные у
nothing antique I mean not
меня ничего старинного не в смысле не
antique hinges hinges are still Soviet
старинные петли петли ещё советские
hinges on the door that's for
петли у двере это
sure I myself am still Soviet I'm telling you
точно я сам ещё Советский Я же говорю
these are the doors in short I don't make them like that now
это эти двери короче таких сейчас не
Yes yes I could of course hang a
выпускаю Да да я мог бы конечно повесить
flag like that you know that you have scotch tape
флаг такой у тебя зна что у тебя
because I see that you covered the torn
скотч потому что я вижу что ты порванные
wallpaper with scotch tape it's reflecting yes it's not this
обои залепил скотчем он отсвечивает да
these Well yes probably scotch tape
это не это эти А ну да наверное скоч
scotch Yes I can see probably yes And that's
скотч Да я же вижу наверно да И что
just not interesting well interesting I'll
просто неинтересно ну интересно вот я
tell you Well yes Well yes I am like that but I don't feel like it I do
тебе скажу Ну да Ну да я так а мне не
n't want to I'm lazy I feel so
охота я не хочу мне Мне лень Мне так
good And why did you cover it with scotch tape well it
хорошо А зачем скотчем залепил ну оно
was cool vintage If only it were like that
было прикольно винтажное Если бы оно так
Well you find it so cool And I find it so cool well that is how
Ну тебе так прикольно А мне так
much do you care about this
прикольно ну то есть тебе до это сколько
pension How much is your
пенси Сколько у тебя
pension I'm going to report to you now or what Yes
пенсия Я сейчас тебе буду отчитываться
report yes you'll get by
отчита да перебьёшься
let's go from the other side Look now they
давай с другой стороны зайдём
kicked this out of the
Смотри вот сечас это выгнали там из
oval office of yours wait
овального кабинета вашего это подожди
wait I  I understand correctly you are sitting
подожди я правильно понимаю ты сидишь
here in this oh in vintage Yes and you are worried about what is
вот в этом ой в винтаже Да и Переживаешь
going on there between Ukraine and the USA I
что там короче между Украиной и США я
understand correctly let's do it differently if those so again once again
понимаю давай по-другому если те так ещё
stop I understand correctly you are
раз ещё раз стоп я правильно понимаю ты
sitting in a
сидишь в
hopeless you have lived your whole life in this
беспросветный ты прожил всю жизнь в этой
hopelessness
беспро
such although in your old age or your
сде такы хотя на старости жизни или твои
children grandchildren have lived normally you
дети внуки пожили нормально ты что-то
say something you haven't washed for years
говоришь года не мылся
remember remember Yes
помнишь помни Да
Yano And I do the same
Яно А мне так
Ravi Why do you like to
Рави Почему те нравится
live not me
жить не я
if you look back and think Well if it
если ты оглянешься и подумаешь Ну если
were something for you you understood that it is
бы тебе было чем то ты понял что это вы
all of you and then the main thing is different if
все и потом главное другое вот если бы
you also had brains for example I
ещё у тебя были мозги к примеру я так
hypothetically estimate so then there is a
гипотетически так прикидываю то вот
country nearby called Belarus
рядом есть страна называется Белорусь
they live like people but you live like
они живут как люди а вот вы живёте как
Belarusians Yes just like you that's
белорусы живут Да так же как и вы вот
normal not normal not people And why is it
нормально не нормально не люди А почему
good the question is why Belarusians live like
хорошо вопрос почему белорусы живут как
people and you live in
люди а вы жите в
Why don't you want to live like
Почему ты не хочешь жить как
Belarusians This is your personal opinion it doesn't
белорусы Это твоё личное мнение это не
know I see I see I see Belarusians they
знат я вижу я вижу я вижу белорусов они
live normally And you
нормально живут А ты
you are all-seeing I understand you have it
жи всевидящий я же понимаю у вас же там
all so cool look and when will this
всё это так круто смотри а когда вот это
Ukraine end and what do you think in
самая Украина кончится а как ты думаешь
your opinion in your opinion look in
на твой взгляд на твой взгляд смотри на
my opinion I think that this
мой взгляд Я думаю что в этом
year Kupala Yes and maybe even until Easter and
году Купала Да а может даже до Пасхи а
Ukraine will live
Украина будет жить
forever
вечно
Amen
Аминь
dude this feature is
чувак вот эта особенность
just simply brutal they are sitting
просто это просто жесть они сидят
in it sealed with tape
в у него скотчем залепленные
Ukraine will end simply
Укра закончится просто
brutal writing on my Telegram right now
жесть пись на мий Telegram прям зараз
axis VN
ось ВН
apok this is very and very important YouTube is busy with
апок це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube заня
us through scarg ORV in your ban and very
нас через скарг ОРВ в твый бан и дуже
many videos I do not show people at times I do not
багато вдео не показую людям вчасно не
show information about streams so that
показуе информация про стримы тому для
we Mali operational links are
того щоб мы Мали оперативный звязок
written right now and Popik there in
пишиться прямо зараз а Попик там в
telegrams will okrim video also interesting and
телеграми окрим видео ще теж цикава и
useful information and we are obliged to you
корисна информация и мы повинни з вами
trimati constant operational links
тримати постийний оперативный звязок
independently in that chi will show you
незалежно в того чи покаже вам проце
YouTube process Slava ukraini
YouTube Слава украини
write a
пиши а